

MOHAMMAD SHAHIN A. ABDUL ZAMAD

BS Information Technology Major in Database

ABOUT ME

Shahin is a BS-IT major in database graduate, competent in back-end development for both web and desktop applications. By being involved in numerous IT projects and exposed in ICT field for over 4 years, he acquired a good foundation in software engineering, web development and project management skills. He is now seeking to apply his skills and enthusiasm in your company from which he believes would help him improve and develop new skills essential to the working industry.

PERSONAL

Date of Birth: 29 May 1998
Birth place: Lanao del Norte
Nationality: Filipino
Marital Status: Single

CONTACT ME

Address: Iligan City Phone: +639361877324 E-mail: mshahinaz29@gmail.com LinkedIn: mshahinaz29@gmail.com

Education

BS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Mindanao State University - Iligan Institute of Technology Major in Database Systems (2014-2018)

*Cum Laude

*DOST Academic Excellence Awardee

Eligibility

Civil Service Eligibility

Career Service Professional Examination 12/03/2018

Work Experience

Team Lead/ Senior Web Developer

Pixzel Digital | January 2021- Present

- Supervised and lead a team of 5 during the development of an ERP (Enterprise resource planning) Project for a construction company.
- Deployed an Online School Registration Portal based on Singapore

Junior Web Developer

Pixzel Digital | October 2018- December 2020

- Developed an Order and Inventory Management System for a Medicine Supplier in Iligan City
- Developed and deployed an Accounting System to a School
- Developed a Warehouse Management System with eCommerce for a Hardware Company
- Developed and deployed an eCommerce, Inventory and POS System on multiple Pharmacies

Intern Developer

Pixzel Digital | January 2018- June 2018

• Fix bugs on an existing website and Run System Testing

Organizations

MSU-IIT DOST Scholars Association (2014-2018) -Member

MSU-IIT Muslim Student Association (2014-2018) -Committee head

Junior Information Technology Society (2014-2018) -Member

EXPERTISE

SKILLS

PHP/Laravel	Web Development
HTML&CSS	Computer
Java —	Computer Programming
	Database
SQL	Database Administration
C/C++	Project Management
Javascript	Management —
Photoshop	Data analytics

References

Roy Aldwin S. Dumaguin

Pixzel Digital Managing Director zacheocreative@gmail.com

Vahn Marty Cagalawan

Senior Developer/Mentor vahnmarty@gmail.com